cli.gs 2011-07-24

# cli.gs: Privacy Policy

Privacy is very important for us and so we would like to explain our policies and practices Cligs uses to manage your information.

## Which Websites Are Covered?

This privacy policy covers both [Cligs](http://cli.gs/) and the [Cligs Blog](http://blog.cli.gs/).

## The Information We Collect

Broadly speaking, we collect two types of information:

  * General statistics for running the service. This includes the traffic details for the Cligs. the Cligs Blog, and for each clig hit. The details are the standard traffic details: browsers, when the hits came in, remote IP addresses, and other HTTP header. They are not used in a personally identifiable way but in aggregate to analyze them in order to optimize the site and service.
  * In order to have an account, we ask you to provide an email address. This is the only personally identifiable info we require. We will not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your email address to other parties. We will use your email address in order to contact you if there is a major change happening in relation to your account.

## Cookies

To technically enable running your account, your browser will need cookies enabled and Cligs will identify your session with a cookie. If you delete this cookie, you will be automatically logged out.

The cookies automatically expire after 30 days. This means your account will remain logged in for those 30 days since last action while logged in. An action can be visiting the site, creating a clig, etc. You can log out at any time by clicking on the log out link.

## Data Security

For your data security and ours, Cligs takes good measures to protect against unauthorized access to the site. This includes a strategy to fight against scrapers and other malicious robots.

If you see a problem, please contact us and we will fix it.

## Privacy Policy Changes

The Cligs service and this Privacy Policy will change over time, we hope for the better to serve your needs better. These changes will be announced on the Cligs Blog and this Privacy Policy will be updated as necessary.
